<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mohamad Ghassany</title>
    <description>Data scientist</description>
    <link>http://mghassany.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://mghassany.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes Probabilités 2 2018/2019</title>
        <description>
          
          Vous trouverez d’abord une comparaison entre les notes des contôles continus et de l’examen. Ensuite, voici la répartition des notes de l’examen selon groupe de TD. La figure est interactive. La note s’affichera en mettant le curseur sur le point de la figure. Le nom de l’étudiant s’affiche si sa...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/notes-probas19/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/notes-probas19/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes CC2 Probabilités 2</title>
        <description>
          
          Vous pouvez voire ci dessous la répartition des notes du CC2 en probabilités 2 selon groupe de TD. La figure est interactive. La note s’affichera en mettant le curseur sur le point de la figure. Le nom de l’étudiant s’affiche si sa note est supérieure ou égale à 14 ....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/notes-cc2-probas19/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/notes-cc2-probas19/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My TimeLine Viz</title>
        <description>
          
          I created, for fun, a timeline visualization since my master degree. I created it using R library timevis. I included the app in Shiny apps. I used the the groups visualization and modified the css file. Here is my timeline. You can zoom in/out, to see for example at what...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/my-timetable/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/my-timetable/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Generating statistical tables</title>
        <description>
          
          Inspired from Arthur Charpentier’s blog post here are some codes to create beautiful statistical tables using R and export them to use in latex. Normal distribution table First tables show the values of \(\Phi\), which are the values of the cumulative distribution function of the normal distribution. 1 2 3...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/generating-statistical-tables/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/generating-statistical-tables/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Credits</title>
        <description>
          
          This site is powered by Jekyll using a modified version of the beautiful-jekyll theme. Some icons are loaded using Font Awesome and Academicons. List of publications is generated using Jekyll Scholar. The contact form is powered by Formspree. I use Sublime Text and some of its wonderful packages to edit...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/this-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/this-website/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll-scholar</title>
        <description>
          
          This post is from Stefan Lankes. It helped me to show my publications on this website. Here it is: I have migrated my blog from Wordpress to Jekyll. Jekyll is the better choice for my workflow and there exist quite a few nice open source themes. For instance, jekyllthemes.org provides...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/From-Wordpress-to-Jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/From-Wordpress-to-Jekyll/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Test markdown</title>
        <description>
          Each post also has a subtitle - 
          This is an original post from the creator of the template to test Markdown. You can write regular markdown here and Jekyll will automatically convert it to a nice webpage. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://mghassany.com/blog/test-markdown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mghassany.com/blog/test-markdown/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
